{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"344","question":"\"Mathematics\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d)"},{"q_number":"345","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"346","question":"\"Zeero\" \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"347","question":" \" \u0d32\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d48"},{"q_number":"348","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":" 1729"},{"q_number":"349","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d43 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?","answer":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"350","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d37\u0d43"},{"q_number":"351","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d43\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"352","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43"},{"q_number":"353","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 .\r\ni.e, 525, 323, 848....."},{"q_number":"354","question":"\"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d43\u0d02."},{"q_number":"355","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43"},{"q_number":"356","question":"Ramanujan Institute of Mathematics ","answer":"CHENNAI"},{"q_number":"357","question":"Binomial \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"358","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"359","question":"Google \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"10 race to 100"},{"q_number":"360","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"10 race to 9"},{"q_number":"361","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"362","question":"\u0d2a\u0d48 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 14"},{"q_number":"363","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"16"},{"q_number":"457","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"1"},{"q_number":"458","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 .\u0d0f\u0d34\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41.\r\n\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d34\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d02?","answer":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02."},{"q_number":"459","question":"20 x 36x 42x 84 x O = ?","answer":"0"},{"q_number":"460","question":"0, I, 2 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d06\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"210"},{"q_number":"461","question":" \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d28\u0d46\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d34\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 49. \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ?","answer":"69"},{"q_number":"462","question":" \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d 50 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32.\r\n\u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d, 2 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 2 \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ?","answer":"200 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a"},{"q_number":"463","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"464","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f 5 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d.\r\n\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f 3 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02"},{"q_number":"465","question":"1 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d 1000 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f ?","answer":"999"},{"q_number":"466","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d16\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f?","answer":"0"},{"q_number":"655","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d06\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"667","question":"11,13,17,23,31, ___ ,\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"41"},{"q_number":"668","question":"1X 2 X 3 X 0 X 4 x 1 =?\r\n","answer":"0"},{"q_number":"669","question":"\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1063","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02","answer":"2012"},{"q_number":"1064","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02","answer":"\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c22"},{"q_number":"1065","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02","answer":"887 Dec:22"},{"q_number":"1066","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f","answer":"1729"},{"q_number":"1067","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d48\u0d25\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1068","question":"\u0d06\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d31\u0d46\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46"},{"q_number":"1069","question":"\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1070","question":"\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1071","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7e","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1072","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"1073","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1074","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1075","question":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1076","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1077","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1078","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1079","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d7b","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7d"},{"q_number":"1080","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"1081","question":"\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1082","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d46"},{"q_number":"1083","question":"\u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02(+),\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d28\u0d02(-)\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1084","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d57\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1085","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b","answer":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"1086","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d02","answer":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f"},{"q_number":"1087","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24","answer":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1088","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1089","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d02 100 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f","answer":"\u0d17\u0d42\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"1090","question":"1\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 100 \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02","answer":"25"},{"q_number":"1091","question":"10 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15","answer":"55 ( \u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46 5050)\r\n"},{"q_number":"1092","question":"\u0d28\u0d42\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 9\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d","answer":"20"},{"q_number":"1093","question":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1094","question":"\u0d2a\u0d48 (\u03c0)\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":" 3.14 ( 22\/7)"},{"q_number":"1095","question":"\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d26\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46"},{"q_number":"1096","question":"10 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ","answer":"\u0d26\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1097","question":"2 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u2018 ","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1098","question":"\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e","answer":"0 & 1"},{"q_number":"1099","question":"\"Mathematics\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 (\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d) ( \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 )\r\n"},{"q_number":"1100","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1101","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d32\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"16"},{"q_number":"1102","question":"\" \u0d32\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d48"},{"q_number":"1103","question":"\u0d2a\u0d48 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 14"},{"q_number":"1104","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d43 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?","answer":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d33 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1105","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43 \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d37\u0d43"},{"q_number":"1106","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"1107","question":" \"Zeero\" \u0d07\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"1108","question":"\u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"1109","question":"Google \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":" 10 race to 100\r\n"},{"q_number":"1110","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"10 race to 9"},{"q_number":"1111","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d43\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d43\u0d02 \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d21\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"1112","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d24 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43"},{"q_number":"1113","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43.....\r\ni.e, 525, 323, 848....."},{"q_number":"1114","question":"\"\u0d38\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d1c\u0d43\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1115","question":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d43"},{"q_number":"1116","question":"Binomial \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d43\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1117","question":"\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02-\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15","answer":"180\u00b0"},{"q_number":"1118","question":"\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d?","answer":" a + b + c "},{"q_number":"1119","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d1c \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d02.- \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?","answer":"3a "},{"q_number":"1120","question":" \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02- \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?","answer":"2(\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f)"},{"q_number":"1121","question":"\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02- \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02=?","answer":" _____________--\r\n\u221a\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02\u00b2+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u00b2"},{"q_number":"1122","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?","answer":"4a"},{"q_number":"1123","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02=?","answer":"\u221a2a"},{"q_number":"1124","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 (Parallogram)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d =?","answer":"2 (a+b) "},{"q_number":"1125","question":"\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d02(Trapezium)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d=?","answer":"Sum of Total Sides."},{"q_number":"1126","question":"\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 (Circle)-\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d=?","answer":"2\u03c0r"},{"q_number":"1127","question":"\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15 (Cone)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"\u2153\u03c0r\u00b2h"},{"q_number":"1128","question":"\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d02(Cylinder) -\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"\u03c0r\u00b2h"},{"q_number":"1129","question":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d02 (Sphere).\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":" \u2074\u2044\u2083\u03c0r\u00b3"},{"q_number":"1130","question":"\u0d05\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d02 (Hemisphere)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"\u00b2\u2044\u2083 \u03c0r\u00b3"},{"q_number":"1131","question":"\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cuboid)-\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02x\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3fx \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1132","question":"\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cuboid)-\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d02=?","answer":"\u221a\u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02\u00b2+\u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f\u00b2+\u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02\u00b2"},{"q_number":"1133","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cube)-a \u0d35\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e:\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"a\u00b3"},{"q_number":"1134","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f (Cube)- a \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e:\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02=?","answer":"a\u00b2h"}]},"code":"100"}